{
    "id": "2d2cc25eafb3441e839775912bc654ea",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He showed ……………………………. late.",
            "description": "To show up is to arrive late. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t mind your coming late, but don’t wake me ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He never wasted a single opportunity to show ............................... his wealth.",
            "description": "To show off is to demonstrate haughtily.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The child was told to keep ............................... from the pond.",
            "description": "To keep away is to remain at a distance.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She passed ............................. before she could utter a word.",
            "description": "To pass out is to faint.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He went .............................. to talk amidst protests.",
            "description": "To go on is to continue. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We don't have a lot of money. We just manage to get ...............................",
            "description": "To get by is to survive.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When they sprinkled cold water on his face, he came .................................. again.",
            "description": "To come to is to regain consciousness.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "to",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His rude behavior put me ...................................",
            "description": "Put off can mean deter or discourage.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Grandpa often drops ................................",
            "description": "To drop by is to visit without appointment.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "by",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was late because the car broke .............................. on the way.",
            "description": "To break down is to stop functioning.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was let ................................. with a warning.",
            "description": "To let somebody off is to punish them lightly. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}